You're right!
They're super light!
These shoes make me feel like I'm floating!
This is awesome!
The future!
They even had a tropical style.
You look great, Jinbe!
Yeah? It's just right for a disguise.
Although maybe we're past that point...
Well, I'm gonna go find a weapon
and teach Vegapunk a lesson.
See you.
Take care of yourself, Bonney!
Thanks a bunch!
Hey!
It's Kuma.
Kuma?!
Is it just me, or is he looking for us?
Guys, move!
What?!
He's gonna charge!
He's after us!
Hey!
What's going on? Fill me in!
Just keep running!
Oh, crap!
Dine and dash. Shoplifting.
Here comes the laser!
I didn't know I needed to pay!
It came out when I kicked it!
That's vandalism, Luffy.
They're gonna kill us over a dine and dash?!
It is a bit excessive.
We gotta fight back or we're in trouble!
We may be pirates, but this is self-defense.
Alright! I didn't want to do this, but...
Gum-Gum...
Wait!
Hey! What's your problem, Bonney?!
If he's gonna shoot lasers,
at least let me punch–
That's my dad...
The only...
family I have left!
What?!
Your dad who was turned into a cyborg...
...is Kuma?!
So please!
Don't hurt my daddy!
Run, you dummy!
It's a pacifista!
Bonney!
A Stretch of Sea
New World
Close valve two!
Seal it, quickly!
Here, too!
Something dead ahead!
Dodge it!
It's no good, Captain!
We can't give them the slip!
As if I'd let you escape!
One more hit like that,
and the water pressure will crush the ship!
No getting away now!
Let's surface.
To the nearby shore! Head northeast!
– Aye aye, Captain!
Head for land!
Hard to starboard!
Prepare for battle! Hurry!
What happened to me?
Anyway, we're in trouble!
– You're so cute, Captain!
Say that again and I'll end you!
– But you are!
Oh, crap!
Even I...
My sex has been changed!
Don't touch the infected!
S-Sorry...
It's an ability that spreads infections!
It changes your sex!
I learned something in my battles
against the Emperors, though.
It's possible to break through it!
If you use enough haki...
you can nullify devil fruit powers!
We surfaced, Captain!
I'm cured!
Good.
That's our captain!
There's no time to relax.
Dock the ship! We're going ashore!
– Aye aye, sir!
He managed to cure the disease, huh?
Guess he lives up to that
three-billion-berry bounty.
That's right.
The antibodies of the cured spread
just like the disease itself.
I trust you enjoyed my feminization disease.
Doc Q
(Sick-Sick Fruit)
Burgess! Let's move to the island.
Van Augur
(Warp-Warp Fruit)
Right on!
What?! The mountain is moving!
Hey! There's someone deep in the island!
These Strong-Strong Fruit powers are the best!
Jesus Burgess
(Strong-Strong Fruit)
Burgess?!
How is he picking up an entire mountain?!
When did they even get here?!
It must be another devil fruit.
Superhuman strength,
contagion, teleportation:
Devil-fruit hunting has landed
them some ridiculous powers!
No wonder their bounties keep going up!
Room!
Amputate!
Long time no see, Trafalgar Law!
Blackbeard!
Why are you here?!
Don't be like that!
We're both members of the Worst Generation!
Commodore!
Stronger says you're too heavy...
and I agree...
Stronger
(Horse-Horse Fruit: Pegasus
Mythical Type)
Between you, Straw Hat, and Kid...
I knew one of you would be
coming here from Wano!
I can't believe Kaido and Big Mom went down!
The world has been turned upside down!
And I'm loving it!
Of course, Kaido had one, didn't he?
How many have you guys found?
I'll be helping myself
to all of your lode poneglyphs!
Right back at you!
The winner...
takes all!